Correspondence, 1920-2007
Smithsonian Institution Archives
- Box 11
  - Sousa, W. P. (Box 11 of 13)
  - Sea-See, 1975 (Box 11 of 13)
  - Sei-Sel, 1992 (Box 11 of 13)
  - Ses-Sez, 1977 (Box 11 of 13)
  - Sha, 1983-1992 (Box 11 of 13)
  - Shi, 1975-1983 (Box 11 of 13)
  - She, 1981-1983 (Box 11 of 13)
  - Sho-Shu, 1977 (Box 11 of 13)
  - Sia-Sil, 1975-1982 (Box 11 of 13)
  - Sim, 1982-1989 (Box 11 of 13)
  - Sin-Siz, 1978-1981 (Box 11 of 13)
  - Sk, 1978 (Box 11 of 13)
  - Sl, 1978-1982 (Box 11 of 13)
  - Sm, 1983-1993 (Box 11 of 13)
  - Sn-Sny, 1978-1982 (Box 11 of 13)
  - So-Sop, 1986 (Box 11 of 13)
  - Spa-Spe, 1977-1979 (Box 11 of 13)
  - Sph-Spo, 1978-1999 (Box 11 of 13)
  - Spr-Spu, 1979-1987 (Box 11 of 13)
  - Sq-Sr, 1983-1987 (Box 11 of 13)
  - St-Stan, 1975-182 (Box 11 of 13)
  - Stao-Staz, 1979-1982 (Box 11 of 13)
  - Stea-Steg, 1975 (Box 11 of 13)
  - Steh-Sten, 1977-1988 (Box 11 of 13)
  - Steo-Steq, 1982-1992 (Box 11 of 13)
  - Ster-Steu, 1976-1981 (Box 11 of 13)
  - Stev-Stez, 1952-1986 (Box 11 of 13)
  - Sti (Box 11 of 13)
  - Sto-Stok, 1975-1985 (Box 11 of 13)
  - Stol-Stoz, 1978-1985 (Box 11 of 13)
  - Stra-Stre, 1984-1986 (Box 11 of 13)
  - Stro-Stry, 1984 (Box 11 of 13)
  - Stu, 1979-1985 (Box 11 of 13)
  - Su-Suz, 1975-1987 (Box 11 of 13)
  - Sw, 1975-1987 (Box 11 of 13)
  - Smith, A-F (Box 11 of 13)
  - Smith, G-J (Box 11 of 13)
  - Smith, L-S (Box 11 of 13)
  - Smith, Allyn G. (Box 11 of 13)
  - Solem, Alan (Box 11 of 13)
  - Stansberry, David H. (Box 11 of 13)
  - Stuardo, Jose (Box 11 of 13)
  - T, 2003 (Box 11 of 13)
  - T, 1999 (Box 11 of 13)
  - T, 1998 (Box 11 of 13)
  - T, 1997 (Box 11 of 13)
  - T, 1996 (Box 11 of 13)
  - T, 1995 (Box 11 of 13)
  - T, 1994 (Box 11 of 13)
  - T, 1993 (Box 11 of 13)
  - T, 1992 (Box 11 of 13)
  - T, 1991 (Box 11 of 13)
  - T, 1990 (Box 11 of 13)
  - T, 1989 (Box 11 of 13)
  - Ta-Tam, 1978-1980 (Box 11 of 13)
  - Tan-Tav, 1981-1987 (Box 11 of 13)
  - Taw-Taz, 1976-1981 (Box 11 of 13)
  - Tea-Tek, 1977-1980 (Box 11 of 13)
  - Tel-Tez, 1976-1986 (Box 11 of 13)
- Box 12
  - Tia-Tim, 1980-1988 (Box 12 of 13)
  - Tha-Thol, 1978-1986 (Box 12 of 13)
  - Thomas (Box 12 of 13)
  - Thom-Thoz, 1970-1988 (Box 12 of 13)
  - Tin-Tiz, 1981-1986 (Box 12 of 13)
  - To, 1970-1990 (Box 12 of 13)
  - Tra-Tre, 1980-1985 (Box 12 of 13)
  - Tri-Tru, 1978-1986 (Box 12 of 13)
  - Tu-Tuq, 1978-1985 (Box 12 of 13)
  - Tur, 1986 (Box 12 of 13)
  - Tw, 1979 (Box 12 of 13)
  - Ty, 1982-1988 (Box 12 of 13)
  - Talmadge, R. R. (Box 12 of 13)
  - Taylor, John D. (Box 12 of 13)
  - Teskey, Margaret (Box 12 of 13)
  - Thompson (Box 12 of 13)
  - Toll (Box 12 of 13)
  - Trondle, Jean (Box 12 of 13)
  - Turner, Ruth D. (Box 12 of 13)
  - U, 1996 (Box 12 of 13)
  - U, 1993 (Box 12 of 13)
  - U, 1990 (Box 12 of 13)
  - U, 1989 (Box 12 of 13)
  - U, 1970-1980 (Box 12 of 13)
  - V, 2000 (Box 12 of 13)
  - V, 1999 (Box 12 of 13)
  - V, 1998 (Box 12 of 13)
  - V, 1997 (Box 12 of 13)
  - V, 1995 (Box 12 of 13)
  - V, 1996 (Box 12 of 13)
  - V, 1991 (Box 12 of 13)
  - V, 1994 (Box 12 of 13)
  - V, 1993 (Box 12 of 13)
  - V, 1990 (Box 12 of 13)
  - V, 1989 (Box 12 of 13)
  - V, 1992 (Box 12 of 13)
  - Van Mol (Box 12 of 13)
  - Van (Box 12 of 13)
  - Vao-Vaz, 1981-1986 (Box 12 of 13)
  - Vea-Van, 1975-1984 (Box 12 of 13)
  - Veo-Vez, 1975-1981 (Box 12 of 13)
  - Via-Vik, 1981-1984 (Box 12 of 13)
  - Vil-Vl, 1978-1988 (Box 12 of 13)
  - Voa-Vom, 1979-1987 (Box 12 of 13)
  - Von-Voz, 1987-1988 (Box 12 of 13)
  - Van De-Van Der (Box 12 of 13)
  - Van Der Schalie, H. (Box 12 of 13)
  - Vokes, H. E. Vokes, E. H. (Box 12 of 13)
  - Voss, Gil, 1970- (Box 12 of 13)
  - Voss, Gil, 1960- (Box 12 of 13)
  - W, 2007 (Box 12 of 13)
  - W, 2001 (Box 12 of 13)
  - W, 1999 (Box 12 of 13)
  - W, 1997 (Box 12 of 13)
  - W, 1998 (Box 12 of 13)
  - W, 1996 (Box 12 of 13)
  - W, 1995 (Box 12 of 13)
  - W, 1994 (Box 12 of 13)
  - W, 1993 (Box 12 of 13)
  - W, 1992 (Box 12 of 13)
  - W, 1991 (2 folders) (Box 12 of 13)
  - W, 1990 (Box 12 of 13)
  - W, 1989 (Box 12 of 13)
  - Wa-Wak, 1978-1984 (Box 12 of 13)
  - Wal, 1975-1984 (Box 12 of 13)
  - War, 1970-1990 (Box 12 of 13)
  - Was-Wat, 1982-2005 (Box 12 of 13)
  - Wau-Wax, 1975-1981 (Box 12 of 13)
  - We-Web, 1977-1988 (Box 12 of 13)
  - Webe-Wed, 1981 (Box 12 of 13)
  - Wel, 1976-1978 (Box 12 of 13)
  - Weh-Wek, 1986 (Box 12 of 13)
  - Va-Vam, 1975-1988 (Box 12 of 13)
  - Well, 1976-1982 (Box 12 of 13)
  - Wem-Weq, 1986 (Box 12 of 13)
  - Wer-Wes, 1972-1982 (Box 12 of 13)
  - Wet-Wez, 1976-1982 (Box 12 of 13)
  - Wh-Whee, 1975 (Box 12 of 13)
  - Whi, 1975-1978 (Box 12 of 13)
- Box 13
  - Why, 1977 (Box 13 of 13)
  - Wi-Wil, 1973-1985 (Box 13 of 13)
  - Wim-Win, 1975-1990 (Box 13 of 13)
  - Wells, J. W. (Box 13 of 13)
  - Williamson, Gordon (Box 13 of 13)
  - Wio-Wiz, 1993 (Box 13 of 13)
  - Wo-Wom, 1975-1986 (Box 13 of 13)
  - Woo-Wood, 1982-1993 (Box 13 of 13)
  - Wooda-Woodv, 1975-1982 (Box 13 of 13)
  - Woodw, 1988 (Box 13 of 13)
  - Wooe-Woz, 1980-1988 (Box 13 of 13)
  - Wright (Box 13 of 13)
  - Wri, 1988 (Box 13 of 13)
  - Wu, 1976-1988 (Box 13 of 13)
  - Wyn, 1977 (Box 13 of 13)
  - Williams Williamson (Box 13 of 13)
  - Wilson, Barry (Box 13 of 13)
  - Wilson, Barry R. (Box 13 of 13)
  - XYZ, 1995 (Box 13 of 13)
  - XYZ, 1994 (Box 13 of 13)
  - XYZ, 1997 (Box 13 of 13)
  - XYZ, 1992 (Box 13 of 13)
  - XYZ, 1991 (Box 13 of 13)
  - XYZ, 1990 (Box 13 of 13)
  - XYZ, 1993 (Box 13 of 13)
  - XYZ, 1989 (Box 13 of 13)
  - Ya-Ye, 1979-1981 (Box 13 of 13)
  - Yo, 1975-1990 (Box 13 of 13)
  - Zetek, James (Box 13 of 13)
  - Zh-Zi, 1975-1981 (Box 13 of 13)
  - Zo-Zu, 1976 (Box 13 of 13)
  - Zw, 1981 (Box 13 of 13)
  - Visitor Guidelines (Box 13 of 13)
  - Cites Permits, import and export (2 folders) (Box 13 of 13)
  - Missing M2O Microscope (Box 13 of 13)
  - Rehder, Harald A. (Box 13 of 13)
  - Record (guest book), 1938-1975 (Box 13 of 13)
  - Record/Guest book, 1975-1987 (Box 13 of 13)
  - Collection Status Report (Box 13 of 13)
  - Systematics Labor Story Agreement (Box 13 of 13)
  - Division of Mollusks Archives (Box 13 of 13)
  - Endangered species (Box 13 of 13)
  - Problem transactions (Box 13 of 13)
  - Accessions - Annual report (Box 13 of 13)
  - 1979-1980 Annual Report (Box 13 of 13)
  - Department Review (Box 13 of 13)
  - Accessions 1980-1981 fiscal year (2 folders) (Box 13 of 13)
  - Accessions 1981-1982 fiscal year (Box 13 of 13)